{
    "subject": "resource/Adam_Schlesinger",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Adam Schlesinger is the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9308497905731201,
            "question": "Adam Schlesinger's hometown is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8811279535293579,
            "question": "What country is Adam Schlesinger's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8795387744903564,
            "question": "Was Adam Schlesinger born in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8546120524406433,
            "question": "Is Adam Schlesinger originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7421796321868896,
            "question": "Where was Adam Schlesinger from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615954041481018,
            "question": "Is the United States considered Adam Schlesinger's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52010178565979,
            "question": "Where did Adam Schlesinger grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47488167881965637,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Adam Schlesinger comes from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38367611169815063,
            "question": "Which country can be considered Adam Schlesinger's home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3807547986507416,
            "question": "What is Adam Schlesinger's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Adam Schlesinger is the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9167_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country can be considered Adam Schlesinger's home?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9167_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the country where Adam Schlesinger comes from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9167_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Adam Schlesinger grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9167_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9167_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Adam Schlesinger was born in New York City, but they do not specify if his hometown is the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: All provided documents mention that Adam Schlesinger was born in New York City, USA and grew up there. This supports the statement that his hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "He was born in New York City, New York, USA.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}